const cardData = [
  { question: 'Which state is the furthest north?', answer: 'Alaska' },
  { question: 'In which state is the Grand Canyon?', answer: 'Arizona' },
  { question: 'In which state(s) is Yellowstone National Park?', answer: 'Wyoming, Montana, Idaho' },
  { question: 'How many states begin with the letter A? Name them.', answer: 'Alabama, Arkansas, Arizona, Alaska' },
  { question: 'Which is the longest river in the US?', answer: 'Mississippi River' },
  { question: 'In which state is the "windy city"?', answer: 'Illinois (Chicago)' },
  { question: 'What is the longest US Highway?', answer: 'Route 20' },
  { question: 'Which state has birthed the most US presidents?', answer: 'Virginia' },
  { question: 'What state is the smartest (based on test scores, high school diplomas and college degrees)?', answer: 'Massachusetts' },
  { question: 'Which state motto is "live free or die"?', answer: 'New Hampshire' },
];

export default cardData;